let triviaQuestions = [

    // {question: "Where did Meredith Grey go to College?", 
    //     answers: ["Darmouth College", "Princeton University" , "Prescott College" , "Stanford University"],
    //     theAnswer: 0,
    //     correctAnswer: "<img src='assets/images/darmouth.gif' />",
    //     incorrectAnswer: "<img src='assets/images/soSad.gif' />",
    // },
    
    //1
    {question: "Which of the following characters was never a Defense against the Dark Arts teacher?",
            answers: ["Remus Lupin", "Sturgis Podmore", "Gilderoy Lockhart" , "Severus Snape"],
            theAnswer: 1,

    },
    //2
    {question: "Which of the following classes was taught by Professor Flitwick?",
            answers: ["Arithmancy", "Transformation", "Charms" , "Astronomy"],
            theAnswer: 2,

    },
    //3
    {question: "Who are the two Divination teachers?",
            answers: ["Firenze and Lupin", "Lupin and Trelawny", "Firenze and Trelawny" , "Sprout and Trelawny"],
            theAnswer: 2,
    },
    //4
    {question: "Which of the following classes was taught by Professor Sprout?",
            answers: ["Herbology", "Care of Magical Creatures", "Muggle Studies" , "Potions"],
            theAnswer: 0,

    },
    //5
    {question: "Which of the following characters is NOT an animagus?",
            answers: ["Sirius Black", "Peter Pettigrew", "James Potter" , "Remus Lupin"],
            theAnswer: 3,

    },
    //6
    {question: "Which of the following people took the locket-horcrux from Voldemort's cave and replaced it with a decoy?",
            answers: ["Sirius Black", "Regulus Black", "Bathilda Bagshot" , "Rita Skeeter"],
            theAnswer: 1,
    },
    //7
    {question: "Who is the heir of Slytherin?",
            answers: ["Lucius Malfoy", "Blaise Zabini", "Severus Snape" , "Tom Riddle"],
            theAnswer: 1,
    },
    //8
    {question: "Which of the following is NOT in Diagon Alley?",
            answers: ["Ollivander's Wand shop", "Honeydukes Sweets", "Madame Malkin's robe shop", "Flourish & Botts book shop"],
            theAnswer: 1,
    },
    //9
    {question: "Which of the following is NOT in Hogsmeade?",
            answers: ["Madame Puddifoot's Tea shop", "The Shrieking Shack", "Gringott's Bank", "The Three Broomsticks"],
            theAnswer: 2,
    },
    //10
    {question: "Which of the following characters (surprisingly) comes to Harry's aid, ultimatley contributing to Voldemort's defeat?",
            answers: ["Narcissa Malfoy", "Fenrir Greyback", "Alecto Carrow", "Amycus Carrow"],
            theAnswer: 0,
    },
    //11
    {question: "Which of the following characters caused the destruction of a horcrux without actually meaning to destroy it?",
            answers: ["Mundungus Fletcher", "Xenophilius Lovegood", "Bathilda Bagshot", "Vincent Crabbe"],
            theAnswer: 3,

    },

    {question: "How did the Snatchers/Death Eaters know that Harry, Ron and Hermione were in Hogsmeade just prior to the Battle at Hogwarts?",
    answers: ["Someone had been tracking them through an enchantment", "Griphook betrayed them after the Gringott's stint", "Harry saying the name 'Voldemort' triggered the taboo curse", "They were seen flying on broomsticks"],
    theAnswer: 2,

}

] 